<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF&#45;8"?>
<month>

<d020609>This is test text &#45; Tuesday</d020609>
<d030609>This is test text &#45; Wednesday</d030609>
<d040609>This is test text &#45; Thursday</d040609>
<d050609>This is test text &#45; Friday</d050609>
<d060609>This is test text &#45; Saturday</d060609>
<d070609>This is test text &#45; Sunday</d070609>
<d080609>This is test text &#45; Monday</d080609>
<d090609>This is test text &#45; Tuesday</d090609>
<d100609>This is test text &#45; Wednesday</d100609>


	<d110609>Try doing things in a completely new way today. Start by reading the Club Penguin Times backwards like this &#45; Day Backwards It&apos;s! Luck Good!</d110609>
	<d120609>It&apos;s the day of the big green parade! Paint your penguin any shade of green and start a parade across the island with 20 other green penguins!</d120609>
	<d130609>Start finding! Get a group of friends together and have a race to complete the Adventure Hunt. Be the first to spot everything!</d130609>
	<d140609>Find a buddy and go find a plant that eats snowballs. Hint: Throw snowballs at every plant you see until you find it!</d140609>
	<d150609>Prepare for take&#45;off at the Beacon of the Lighthouse! Play Jet&#45;Pack Adventure and try flying the whole course without getting any coins and win a huge bonus prize!</d150609>
	<d160609>Attention explorers! Grab your best explorer&apos;s outfit and uncover the mysterious stone puffle statue. Lead 10 penguins to it, calling &#147;This way to the stone puffle!&#148;</d160609>
	<d170609>It&apos;s a busy day in the Coffee Shop! Put on your apron and get to work. Serve 10 cups of coffee to thirsty penguins.</d170609>
	
	<d180609>Check out the Dojo igloo contest winners in the newspaper!  Buy some furniture from the catalog in the Ninja Hideout &amp; recreate your favorite in your own igloo!</d180609>
	<d190609>The new pin is out, so make sure you find it and wear it! Help other penguins discover it by giving them clues!</d190609>
	<d200609>Head to the Stage to star in Fairy Fables! Try playing all of the roles, then pick your favorite and put on a play with your buddies.</d200609>
	<d210609>Make buddies with 7 penguins from different countries. Make sure you all wear your country flag pins!</d210609>
	<d220609>Form a sports team with your buddies and start a game at the Soccer Pitch. Choose a team color to wear and make up cheers for your team!</d220609>
	<d230609>Make sure you have all the colors from Penguin Style. Then get together with your friends and throw a color party!</d230609>
	<d240609>Challenge someone to a Card&#45;Jitsu match and earn your next belt. If you&apos;re already a ninja, practice in the secret Ninja Hideout.</d240609>
	
	<d250609>Pretend to sink the Iceberg! Get a bunch of buddies to turn light blue and dance on the Iceberg so that you all look like water on top of the &apos;berg!</d250609>
	<d260609>Ch&#45;ch&#45;check out the new DJ3K tracks in the Night Club today and celebrate by starting a dance party in your igloo! Don&apos;t forget to decorate.</d260609>
	<d270609>At the Pizza Parlor, flick the switch on the Pizzatron 3000 and turn your pizzas sweet! Quickly make 8 candy pizzas without making a mistake.</d270609>
	<d280609>Go Ice Fishing and hook as many fish as you can &#45; then cook your catch for some buddies at a party in your igloo!</d280609>
	<d290609>Time to hit the dance floor and show off your moves! Challenge a buddy to a dance&#45;off in the Night Club.</d290609>
	<d300609>Waddle along to the Coffee Shop and go upstairs to the book room! Read all of the books and then wear the secret item that&apos;s hidden in one of them...</d300609>
	<d010709>Make a buddy smile. Tell your 5 favorite friends that you think they&apos;re terrific by sending a Penguin Mail postcard!</d010709>
	
	<d020709>Put on your Tour Guide hat and take a new penguin around the island, teaching them everything they need to know about Club Penguin! If you&apos;re not a tour guide, take a tour!</d020709>
	<d030709>Sensei&apos;s at the Hideout! Wear your belt around the island and let everyone know that Sensei has come to visit.</d030709>
	<d040709>Celebrate under the fireworks by getting your penguin buddies together at the Iceberg and forming lines of different colors. Then... Dance!</d040709>
	<d050709>Go to the Forest and pretend to be an animal! Try to get 10 different animals there, and pretend to have your own zoo!</d050709>
	<d060709>Travel! Log in and choose the French language! Waddle around and say &#147;Bonjour&#148;!</d060709>
	<d070709>Do Mission #1 &amp; look for a hidden penguin by the Ice Rink. If you&apos;re not a Penguin Secret Agent, join by clicking the M at the top of your screen &amp; take the quiz!</d070709>
	<d080709>&#147;You Decide!&#148; Head to the What&apos;s New Blog and help choose an item for the August Penguin Style catalog! </d080709>

	<d090709>Create a store in your igloo! Pretend you&apos;re the most successful shop&#45;keeper on the island and sell furniture items or pets!</d090709>
	<d100709>Ruby and the Ruby is at the Stage! Go read the script and then be Jacques Hammer or Ruby all over the island. Ask questions about the missing ruby!</d100709>
	<d110709>Play Medieval hide and seek on the island by dressing in your favorite Medieval&#45;style outfit and chasing penguins who say &#147;roar!&#148; If you have a dragon costume, get knights and princesses to chase you!</d110709>
	<d120709>Head to the Penguin Style catalog at the Gift Shop. Get 10 friends to pick a new outfit, grab your camera, and go to the Cove to have a fashion show!</d120709>
	<d130709>Take your puffle to the game it helps you play! Then walk around the island with your pet &amp; let everyone know how awesome your pet is!</d130709>
	<d140709>Go visit 15 igloos &amp; tell the owner something that you love about their igloo.</d140709>
	<d150709>Take your soccer ball to the Iceberg and start a dance party!</d150709>
	
	<d160709>Head to the Portuguese server and say &#147;Penguinando!&#148;. It&apos;s like saying &#147;Waddle on!&#148; See if you can get 5 penguins to say it back.</d160709>
	<d170709>Rock? Country? Pop? Get your outfit, instrument &amp; friends! Check out every stage, pick your favorite, and get 5 penguins dancing!</d170709>
	<d180709>The new furniture is out! Make your igloo the coolest place to rock and then invite 10 penguins to a loud igloo party!</d180709>
	<d190709>Use your All&#45;Access pass to get behind the scenes. Find a penguin to interview about their favorite times jamming with their band!</d190709>
	<d200709>Find a cool band and let them know you&apos;d like to help their success! Grab them a pizza, or dance to their songs.</d200709>
	<d210709>Wackiest Music Jam outfit day. Cram the Lighthouse Stage in your wackiest outfit!</d210709>
	<d220709>Make your igloo into an airplane and pretend to fly all over the world!</d220709>
	
	<d230709>It&apos;s day 50 of 101 Days of Fun! Can you help to get a group of at least 10 penguins on the Iceberg to show happy face emotes?</d230709>
	<d240709>You get to vote for the new penguin color! Head to the Forest and help decide! Cheer for your favorite color around the island.</d240709>
	<d250709>Take your purple or blue puffle out and about and visit other igloos! You can decorate your own igloo (try purple and blue) to host a puffle party.</d250709>
	<d260709>Last day of the Music Jam! Join your friends for a massive &#147;dance off&#148; at your favorite stage.</d260709>
	<d270709>Play the secret hidden game on a computer in Mission #3. If you&apos;re not a Penguin Secret Agent, and are 30 days old, join by clicking the M at the top of your screen &amp; take the quiz!</d270709>
	<d280709>It&apos;s a symphony! Press E and then T to show the music note emote and then get your buddies to fill up an igloo with sound!</d280709>
	<d290709>Take your puffle for a walk around the island and give other penguins tips on how to be the best pet owner ever!</d290709>
	
	<d300709>Starting at the Cove, get at least 10 penguins in a line and walk around the entire island!</d300709>
	<d310709>Transform your igloo into the ultimate performing stage, then invite others to come put on a show!</d310709>
	<d010809>Play one level of every single game on the island.</d010809>
	<d020809>Go to the Stage, grab some detective gear from the catalog and spend some time investigating the island!</d020809>
	<d030809>Find your scuba gear, head down to the Underground Pool, and have a snorkel party!</d030809>
	<d040809>Dance, wave, and sit in any order, then see if other penguins can follow your moves!</d040809>
	<d050809>You Decide! Head to the What&apos;s New Blog to help select a new furniture item!</d050809>
	
	<d060809>Check out Penguins Around the World on the Community page of the website, then send us a picture of your toy penguin preparing for the Festival of Flight!</d060809>
	<d070809>Celebrate the new color release with a game of tag. When you get tagged, turn aqua and pass it on!</d070809>
	<d080809>Have a shopping race with a buddy! Start at the Snow Forts and see if you can run to the Gift Shop, buy a new outfit, then return to the Snow Forts in 1 minute.</d080809>
	<d090809>Form a group with other penguins and pretend you&apos;re a car. Waddle around the island together and give other penguins a lift!</d090809>
	<d100809>Waddle up to the Book Room for a blast from the past. Find the hidden pyramid in the 2007&#45;2008 Yearbook!</d100809>
	<d110809>Be the funniest penguin possible! Go tell everyone your favorite joke on stage at the Lighthouse.</d110809>
	<d120809>Slow down! See if you can be the last penguin down the hill while playing Sled Racing with your buddies.</d120809>
	
	<d130809>What kind of sunglasses does Aunt Arctic wear? Find out by moving your mouse around page B5 of the Club Penguin Times, then tell 5 friends!</d130809>
	<d140809>Find the new pin! When you do, draw attention to it by forming a big circle around it with the other penguins in the area.</d140809>
	<d150809>Transform your igloo into an airplane, then invite other penguins over and watch the fun take flight!</d150809>
	<d160809>Go to the Pet Shop and practice your Puffle Roundup skills. Try capturing the blue puffles first, then the rest, one color at a time! </d160809>
	<d170809>Talk to your buddies using only emotes! See how many times you can make other penguins smile :)</d170809>
	<d180809>Try to find your penguin twin! Look at other penguin&apos;s player cards and see if you can make buddies with a penguin who is dressed&#45;up just like you today!</d180809>
	<d190809>Start a wave at the Cove! Get a bunch of blue penguins together, then as a group walk back and forth in the water shouting &apos;Wave!&apos;</d190809>
	
	<d200809>Start a game of Copy Me at the Night Club. Whatever you do, get your friends to do it too. Try dancing, using emoticons or telling a joke! </d200809>
	<d210809>You&apos;ve caught the rhythm bug, and you can&apos;t stop dancing! Coordinate a conga line of 20 penguins and dance around the island.</d210809>
	<d220809>Describe a Club Penguin character or event to your buddies without saying its name. Feel free to use clothing items as props and see if they can guess it in 5 tries!</d220809>
	<d230809>Head to the Surf Shack at the Cove and play Catchin&apos; Waves in Survival Mode. Try staying on your board long enough to see the shark!</d230809>
	<d240809>Turn your igloo into a superhero HQ and recruit a team of penguins who are eager to help save the day! Your team&apos;s first task, offer to save 10 penguins in need of help.</d240809>
	<d250809>Find a penguin wearing at least 3 clothing items, then try to guess which is their favorite. If someone guesses your favorite item, display a smiley emote!</d250809>
	<d260809>Check out the new play at the Stage! See if you can memorize one character&apos;s lines, then recite them to other penguins around the island.</d260809>
	
	<d270809>Give your throwing flipper some practice! Meet up with your buddies at the Snow Forts and cover the Penguin Stadium sign with as many snowballs as you can.</d270809>
	<d280809>Start a game of soccer at the Soccer Pitch! Get two teams together and see how many goals you can score in a match.</d280809>
	<d290809>Ninjas should exchange Card Jitsu tips in the Hideout! If you don&apos;t have your black belt, head to the Dojo and learn to play Card Jitsu!</d290809>
	<d300809>Become a puzzle master! Start by solving this week&apos;s Puzzle Shuffle in the Club Penguin Times, then check out the Boiler Room for other newspaper puzzles!</d300809>
	<d310809>Let your buddy help design your igloo! Put some furniture items in the middle of your igloo, then ask them where they would put everything!</d310809>
	<d010909>Help your buddies find all the buoys in Club Penguin from 1 &#45; 8. They&apos;re hidden in games, missions and rooms. Good luck!</d010909>
	<d020909>You Decide! Head to the What&apos;s New Blog and help decide on a catalog item!</d020909>
	
	<d030909>Take a shift as a lifeguard at the Underground Pool. Help 5 penguins stay safe by teaching them how to swim.</d030909>
	<d040909>Attention all ninjas! Show up at the Cove wearing your ninja gear, then watch your surroundings closely for a fiery surprise.</d040909>
	<d050909>Start a game show in your igloo and come up with silly prizes for the first 5 winners!</d050909>
	<d060909>Have some fun giving out fashion advice at the Gift Shop. Try to get at least 3 different penguins to wear your favorite new item!</d060909>
	<d070909>Pretend you're in a synchronized swimming team. Get a crowd of at least 10 penguin in the water and make shapes together!</d070909>
	<d080909>All flippers on deck! Climb aboard the Migrator and see how many penguins you can get to climb up the mast to the Crow's Nest.</d080909>
	<d090909>Find the emerald hidden aboard the Migrator by playing Treasure Hunt. Have a buddy help you; emerald hunting is hard work and you won't find one in every game.</d090909>
	
	<d100909>Have some fun playing games at the Fair today! Try collecting 101 tickets as fast as possible. </d100909>
	<d110909>Find a pin made especially for 101 fans! Hint: Walk, waddle, or run to the place that the first 101 activity was done. </d110909>
	<d120909>Hold an igloo party and share stories about your favorite 101 activity, then tell us what you enjoyed most on the What's New blog!</d120909>
	
</month>